Presents aren't the only thing they're unwrapping!
Barely Legal is a comedy film directed by Jose Montesinos.
Sue, Cheryl and Lexi are three college freshmen who have been
best friends since they were born on the same day.
They do something special every year for their birthday, but on
their eighteenth, they set out to lose their virginity.
Cheryl, played by Jeneta St. Clair.
Lexi, played by Lisa Younger.
Sue, played by Melissa Johnston.
Jake, played by Morgan Benoit.
Eric, played by Myko Olivier.
Frank, played by Matthew Keoki Miller.
Barely Legal is a 2011 sex comedy film by The Asylum,
directed by Jose Montesinos and starring Jeneta St.
Clair, Lisa Younger and Melissa Johnston.
The film explores themes of birthday, college, loss of
virginity, best friend, lesbian sex.
The tone is lighthearted.